gotquestions.org 2019-12-19

# What is GotQuestions.org's privacy policy? | GotQuestions.org

[Home](https://www.gotquestions.org/) > [About](https://www.gotquestions.org/about.html) > Privacy

* * *

**Does GotQuestions.org use cookies?**

Yes, GotQuestions.org uses cookies to enhance the user experience. The specific external cookies we employ are listed below. By continuing to use our website, you are agreeing to our privacy policy.

**Does GotQuestions.org record any of my personal information?**

We use [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/) to record, compile, and provide us with reports on our website visitors. The Google Analytics privacy policy is available here: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>.

We use [iContact](https://www.icontact.com/) to record the email addresses of those who choose to subscribe to our newsletter(s). The iContact privacy policy is available here: <https://www.icontact.com/legal/privacy>.

We use [Qgiv](https://www.qgiv.com/) to enable online donations, record the information of those who choose to donate, and process those donations. The Qgiv privacy policy is available here: <https://www.qgiv.com/privacy-policy>.

We use [RefTagger](https://reftagger.com/) to enable Bible verse windows to appear whenever a Scripture reference is selected. The RefTagger privacy policy is available here: <https://reftagger.com/privacy/>.

If a user submits a question to us, the following information is recorded: email address, IP address, the content of the question, and any optional information that is given.

If a user submits a a search query, the following information is recorded: the content of the search query and the IP address.

If a user orders a free promotional material, only the address information the user chooses to enter is recorded.

If a user completes an online survey, only the survey information the user chooses to enter is recorded.

**How does GotQuestions.org store my personal information?**

Please read the privacy policies of Google Analytics, iContact, Qgiv, and RefTagger for their specific data storage policies. For any information collected and recorded explicitly by GotQuestions.org, it is collected over a SSL connection and saved on a secure webserver in a webhosting environment with both hardware and software firewalls. Please understand, though, that no method of transmission or storage on the internet can be guaranteed to provide absolute security.

**What does GotQuestions.org do with my personal information?**

Please read the privacy policies of Google Analytics, iContact, Qgiv, and RefTagger for their specific policies on what they do with the data they collect. For any information collected and recorded explicitly by GotQuestions.org, we use it for the sole purpose of helping to provide a more personal and applicable answer to those who submit questions to us.

**Upon request, will GotQuestions.org delete all record of my personal information?**

Please read the privacy policies of Google Analytics, iContact, Qgiv, and RefTagger for their specific instructions on how to get your personal information deleted from their records. If you send us an email at [questions@gotquestions.org](mailto:questions@gotquestions.org?subject=please%20erase%20my%20personal%20information), we will erase any and all records we have of your personal information. 

* * *

**Return to:

**
